WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
♪ Take me higher ♪
The thing you need to know is,
it's all about sex.
It's true.
In fact, they say men think
about sex every 28 seconds.
Of course, that's straight
men. With gay men it's every 9.
You can be at the
supermarket or the laundromat
or buying a fabulous shirt
when suddenly you find yourself
checking out some hot guy.
Hotter than the one you saw last weekend
or went home with the night before,
which explains why we're all at Babylon
at 1:00 in the morning
instead of at home in bed.
But who wants to be at home in bed?
especially alone, when you can be here,
knowing that at any
moment you might see "him,"
the most beautiful man who ever lived.
That is, until tomorrow night.
By the way, that's me,
6'1," 46-inch chest,
16-inch biceps, 28-inch waist.
A veritable God...
I wish.
Okay, that's me.
Michael Novotny, the semi-cute
"Boy Next Door" type.
"29, 5'10," 140, 9-1/2 cut;
All right, so I exaggerate,
but like, who's told the truth
since they invented cybersex?
When did '70s night become '80s night?
I remember this song from high school.
Talk about feeling ancient.
Speak for yourself,
honey. I was a mere child.
Those are my two buddies,
Ted and Emmett.
Give me those divas of disco any day.
Gloria Gaynor.
- Donna Summer.
- And Miss Alicia Bridges.
- ♪ I love the night life ♪
- Oh!
♪ I like to boogie ♪
♪ On the disco round ♪
♪ Ah-h-h-h ♪
Oh... my God.
Have you ever seen
anything more beautiful?
Venice, at sunset.
Fine, you go down the grand canal,
I'll go down on him.
Ooh...
Emmett can be a little campy.
Okay, a lot campy. But you got to admit,
these days, it takes real guts
to be a queen in a
world full of commoners.
The problem with perfection
is its inability to recognize
anything less perfect than itself.
In other words, you hit on him,
and he turned you down.
Yeah.
Ted's this really smart guy,
and he's got a really big heart.
Only, nobody here is interested
in the size of that organ.
Why am I wasting my time
staring at a bunch of
over-pumped princesses
with IQs smaller than their waist...
Jesus, look at him.
Like I said, it's all about sex.
Except when you're having it.
And then it's all about,
"will he stay? Will he go?
How am I doing? What am I doing?"
Unless, of course, you're Brian Kinney.
And then it's, "who gives
a fuck what you think?"
You're lucky to have me."
I'll get Brian.
- Hey, Todd, how's it going?
- Fine.
We need to go.
We want to eat.
I'm just going to give him my number.
What'd you do, write it on your dick?
How long is this going to take?
Ten minutes.
Tops.
Hmm, Bruno.
Love your outfit.
Not everyone can wear tangerine.
How long are we going to wait?
I've got to work in the morning.
Who doesn't? He said he'd be right out.
Yeah, we've all heard that before.
This is some great system he's got.
He gets to party all night
and you drive him home.
It's no big deal, okay?
Mm. Don't look now but,
uh, somebody's watching.
Oh, him. He has been
cruising me all night.
Mm, playing hard to get.
I love that in a man.
Not playing, just not interested.
Check out that bubble butt.
And that basket.
Enough in there for the big, bad wolf.
Would you quit staring?
There's more to a guy
than his cock size.
Hmm.
Look at that!
Or his perfectly-shaped ass.
Which is why you read
all those comic books
with those superheroes
in their little tights...
For the plot.
I told you, I am not interested.
Well, maybe just for once you should be.
Show a certain someone
he's not the only one
who can score.
'Scuse me.
Uh, could you tell me, like,
where's a good place to go?
Depends what you're looking for.
You want twinkies, go to Boytoy.
You want leather, go to the Meathook.
If you want snotty, conceited assholes
who think they're better than
everybody else, try Pistol.
It's kind of late to be
out, though, isn't it?
Especially on a school night.
Why don't you come home with me, huh?
No thanks.
Go on home to your mommy.
Go on.
That was quick.
Well, when you've had as
much practice as he's had...
I got bored.
I know. Getting your dick
sucked can be so tedious.
Well, he looked pretty hot to me.
Anybody would look hot to you.
And that's when it happened.
When he came along.
How's it going?
You had a busy night?
Just, uh, checking
out the bars, you know?
Boytoy, Meathook.
The Meathook? Really?
So you're into leather?
Sure.
Where you headed?
No place special.
I can change that.
Hey! What about us?
You can ride with Ted.
- Thanks a lot.
- Asshole!
Well, if it isn't miss riding
hood and her big basket.
Find someone else to
stalk. I'm not interested.
Go home.
Coming in?
Hmm?
Oh, yeah.
Shut the door.
This is a... really nice place.
I like your kitchen.
Do you like Special K?
It's okay.
I like Cheerios better.
I don't mean the kind
you eat with bananas.
My disco-pharmacologist
cooks this up for me.
I'm really allergic to a lot of drugs.
The doctor gave me penicillin once...
nearly killed me.
And...
- Tylenol.
- Tylenol?
No one's allergic to Tylenol.
Tylenol's what they give you
when you're allergic to everything else.
Oh.
Well, uh, codeine. Codeine's the worst.
Like, I get diarrhea
and start vomiting
uncontrollably at the same time.
Well, we'll make sure and
keep that one on the top shelf.
Out of reach.
So are you coming or going?
Or coming and then going?
Or coming and staying?
Ohh!
Thank you for the lift.
- See ya.
- Bye.
Oh, my God, look.
He must have followed us.
Christ, that's just what I need.
Honey, it's what we all need.
Hey! When was the
last time you got laid?
My point exactly.
If you can't remember, then it's time.
Now, where are your manners?
Go, uh, go invite the gentleman in
while I make sure none
of my fine washables
are hanging in the tub.
Don't come yet.
Uhh, I'll try.
Stop.
So what do you like to do?
Do?
I don't know.
Watch TV, play Tomb Raider.
I mean in bed.
Oh.
This is fine.
Are you a top or a bottom?
Top...
And bottom.
Oh, you're versatile, then.
And ambidextrous...
Which was really confusing at first
'cause I could never figure
out which hand to throw with.
Do you like to rim?
Sure.
I love it.
Great.
Go to it.
Well?
Um, what exactly do you mean?
Yeah?
What?
When?
Ohh.
Are you kidding me?
No, of course you're not kidding me.
When did it happen?
Why didn't you call me?
Well, of course I was
out. I can't believe it.
- Agh! Ahh!
- Shit!
Jesus Christ! I told you not to.
I tried. I'm sorry.
- All over my new duvet.
- I tried, I tried.
Thank you very much.
Oh, it'll wash out, won't it?
I mean, you should
see my sheets at home.
Just some kid.
What's your name again?
- Justin.
I'll be right there.
Ooh, don't mind me.
Just, uh, can't sleep
without my milk and Oreos.
That's my friend Emmett.
He's staying with me temporarily
since the hooker who lived
down the hall from him
burned his apartment
building down two years ago.
Two years is a long
time to be temporary.
And yet it hasn't
interfered with my love life.
Which, I suppose, says
a lot about my love life.
Do you mind if we skip the back story
and cut to the chase?
It's almost 2:00 in the morning.
You have a great ass.
Oh, yeah?
Ohh.
So do you. It's really...
Firm.
It's called "The Butt."
I got it in a catalogue.
Parts department.
Melanie called. It's happened.
What? Oh my God! When?
I don't know, I had
my damn cell phone off.
I'm picking you up in two minutes.
Now? I...
Kind of got my hands full.
"The Bulge."
You order both, you get a discount.
Who's that?
Uh, no one.
Mikey, you've got
someone there with you.
I can't believe it.
You should only be here.
Forget about it, don't
let me bother you.
Fuck the shit out of him.
No, wait. Pick me up. I'm... I'm ready.
Now.
We going to do this or not?
I am really, really sorry.
Um, a friend of mine needs
me. It's an emergency.
- Shit. After all that?
- I know.
I promise we'll reschedule though.
No ifs, ands or...
- What's going on?
- Everything.
Come on, get up. You gotta go.
- Where?
- Home.
I can't go home now. My...
my parents think I'm
staying at a friend's.
You live with your parents?
Well, I'm still in school.
I mean, college.
- What year are you in?
- Junior.
Sophomore. Between my
junior and sophomore year.
How old are you?
21.
What year were you born?
1979.
Bullshit. You had to think
before you answered that.
How old are you really?
20.
19.
18.
Well, what is this, a missile launch?
17.
What is with kids today?
We just want to get
laid, like everybody else.
Have you ever been with anyone before?
Sure.
Well, not exactly.
This is sort of my first.
I figured.
Kind of young, aren't you?
Well, I was 14 my first time.
- That's really young.
- With my gym teacher.
I bet he was some old perv.
That old perv was probably
the same age that I am now.
It was after school in the locker rooms.
He was taking a shower.
I went back for something.
A book, my jockstrap...
I don't remember.
Anyway, there he was, all
naked, soaping himself.
He saw me there,
a big boner under my chinos.
Shit. I walked right into the showers
with all my clothes on.
No.
Got down on my knees
and sucked him off right there.
He let you?
Let me?
He loved it.
I bet you were scared.
Well, I guess we're all a
little scared our first time.
But I don't remember anymore.
You brought him?
He's got nowhere to go.
Get in.
Jeez.
Oh, my God.
Say hello to your son.
Well, go on.
When did it start?
Around 7:00.
Six hours later, there he was.
Oh, I wish I could have been here.
How often do I get to see snatch?
Looks just like you.
I guess he must be mine then.
Want to hold him?
Okay, careful. Don't drop him.
That's just what I
was planning on doing.
We've been thinking of names.
Mel wants to call him
Abraham, after her grandfather,
but I like Gus.
What do you think?
You wouldn't survive a day
at school being named Abraham.
But I guess Gus is okay.
Thank you very much,
and who the hell are you?
His name's J...
Justin.
You were on the phone when
he shot his load all over me.
Oh, Brian!
He can't help it.
He's only 17.
So you and Lindsay each
had an infant tonight.
Yeah, but mine doesn't suck on my tits.
Not unless I want him to.
"Gus." It's a good, butch name.
Come on, Gus,
give your daddy a smile.
It's disgusting, all those lesbians
fawning over him and
making goo-goo talk.
That's what women do over babies.
Who's talking about
the baby? I mean Justin.
It's kind of weird, you having a kid.
Still, it's exciting, isn't it?
What? Having some wrinkled
little time clock ticking away?
Reminding you that you're
getting older by the minute.
By the second?
Keep thinking like that
you're going to end up prematurely gray.
Oh, I think I see one.
Ow!
Why didn't somebody try and stop me?
Hello? Somebody did.
But you wouldn't listen.
You had to let Lindsay
fill your head with all
her bullshit flattery.
"Oh, Brian, you're so good looking.
Oh, oh, Brian, y...
y... you're so smart.
Oh, oh, you've got
such great genes, Brian,
and I don't mean your 501s."
And now you're stuck with a kid.
For life.
Well, there is always one solution.
I could end it all right now.
Oh, that'd be dramatic.
Just like ER, birth and
death in the same episode.
Now get down!
No, you'll have to come get me.
I'm serious. Stop clowning.
Or I'll jump!
Come on, Mikey, let's fly.
Like in all those comic books.
I'm Superman.
I'll show you the world.
Why am I always Lois Lane?
Congratulations...
Dad.
Sorry.
Honestly.
Fucked him.
You did not. You looked at him.
That may appear to be what happened,
but we did it all.
Oh, yeah? And how was he?
Fabulous.
- Want one?
- No.
More for me.
Listen, you're going to go
say good night to Lindsay.
You're going to go home, go to bed,
and get up and go to
work for the next 20 years
to support your kid.
You see this line, how deep it is?
That means you're very creative.
That's true.
I want to be a cartoonist
or a computer animator.
It's far too lesbianic
out here for a young boy.
Out.
I'll meet you out front.
I'm sorry, sir, you'll
have to come back tomorrow.
The mother needs her rest.
And so does the father.
It's okay, Nurse.
Sweet dreams, Sonny Boy.
First night on earth.
Hon, could you get me some
ice and maybe something fizzy?
How about some ginger ale?
Mm. Mwah.
Uh, anything for you?
Uh, if you see any amyl
nitrate laying around.
Alone at last.
Careful.
Well, here we are.
Ma and Pa.
Hey.
Don't mind me.
Just feeling a little... vulnerable.
I promise not to tell.
Who would have thought?
You and me.
Parents.
It's pretty scary, boys and girls.
- Think it's too late to return it?
- We could try.
I guess this means
we're finally grown-ups.
"Don't say that, Wendy,
we'll never grow up."
Don't be scared.
Hell, if our parents
could fuck up, so can we.
I don't want you to worry.
About money, I mean.
If you need anything...
no, we'll be all right.
But thanks.
I would've fucked you, you know?
Ohh.
If I wasn't afraid
your lover'd beat the shit out of me.
Stop.
I mean it.
She could take out Oscar de la Renta.
You mean La Hoya.
Whatever.
Well, you had plenty of chances.
And I took advantage
of a few, if I recall.
It wasn't half bad.
Now you tell me?
You mean I could have been
straight this whole time?
I wouldn't say that.
Well, then I guess it's just as well.
Ice?
Tick-tick-tick.
Tick.
What are you doing?
I'm just repeating the first words
my Sonny Boy said to me.
It wasn't "da-da."
It was, "tick-tick-tick-tick."
Smart little fucker.
He can tell time already.
Brian, what did you take?
♪ A-b-c-d-e-e-e ♪
I'm just teaching my kid the alphabet.
I'm going to fuck you.
I'm going to fuck you all... night.
Shit!
Sorry, I didn't want to hit that doggie.
Fuck the doggie.
Okay, boy wonder.
I'm taking you home. Where do I turn?
He's going with me.
Oh, no, he's not.
Pop quiz. No talking.
Here's a question. Multiple choice.
Do you want to come home with me?
"A," yes.
"B," yes.
Or "C," yes.
Tick, tick, tick. Time's up.
Pencils down. What do you say?
None of the above.
- He's going home.
- I'm going with him.
Good boy.
You get an A-plus.
Now you know what rimming is.
He calls me, practically
begs me to go with him,
knowing full well I'm with someone
for the first time in
I don't know how long.
Seven months, two weeks, and three days.
Thank you.
And even though the guy wasn't
all he was cracked up to be...
We'll let that remark pass.
At least he wanted me.
Me.
God, I am so horny!
Poor baby.
Well, I have just the thing.
A new porn video.
It all takes place in
a prisoner-of-war camp.
"Hot, horny men starved for action."
I can relate to that.
Guaranteed to make your
privates stand up and salute.
Schindler's Fist?
Here, I will leave you two alone.
I'm sure you're going to have a deep,
meaningful relationship.
Good night.
Okay, private, drop trou and bend over.
For my physical, sir?
No, target practice.
Yes, sir.
Put your legs up...
On my shoulders.
That's it.
Oh, wait.
In school, we had this lecture...
About safe sex.
And now we're going to
have a demonstration.
Ptuh!
Put it on me.
Go on.
Slip it on my dick.
Ah! It's cold.
It'll heat up.
Just...
Go slow, okay?
Agh!
Ah! Ah!
It hurts.
Does it always hurt?
A little bit.
But that's a part of it.
Now relax.
I want you to always remember this.
So that no matter who
you're ever with...
I'll always be there.
What the fuck are you doing here?
You said I could stay.
Right.
Your parents.
They think you're at a friend's.
Jesus Christ! What the hell happened?
Don't tell me.
I was doing handstands.
And juggling.
You're not very good.
Shit.
Why do I do these things?
I'll tell you why.
It was that fucking pig Anita.
She told me that was
"E." That wasn't "E,"
that was some shit they cooked
up in a bathtub in Tijuana.
That's why you should never take drugs
that aren't prescribed by a physician
or recommended by a reliable pharmacist.
What are you,
a public service announcement?
Get dressed, I'll drive you home.
You can't.
- Michael has the car.
- Why has he got it?
- You were too high...
- I know what happened.
I was there.
I remember everything...
Perfectly.
What was your name again?
Justin.
Yeah, right.
Can I take a shower?
Yeah, but hurry up.
It's through there...
I think.
Where the hell are you?
I've been trying your cell.
It's turned off. If
you're there, pick up!
Brian? Listen, Lindsay's water broke.
She's having contractions.
We're at the hospital.
Fuck! I have a baby.
Ow! Ow!
Two babies.
Holy shit!
You little bastards! Get
the fuck away from there!
- Faggot!
- Queer!
Faggot!
Who you calling a faggot?
- We've seen you!
- Fucking queer!
Mornin'.
Oh, my lord.
Motherfuckers!
I'm calling the cops.
Brian is going to have a fit.
You know how he feels about his Jeep.
Well, if he cares so much about it
then he shouldn't have lent it to me.
He knows what a terrible
neighborhood this is.
Well, I, uh, I was going
to ask for a lift to work,
but, on second thought,
I think I'll walk.
Have a nice day.
Shit!
Ahh.
Why didn't you tell me I had a kid?
You said you remembered everything.
Ohh, it all happened so fast.
What's his name again?
Gus.
I'm the one who decided.
Did you actually fuck her?
- Who?
- Lindsay.
- You're awfully rude.
- Well, did you?
I jerked off in a cup,
and they squirted it up her.
Gross.
She must have really wanted a kid.
Most women do.
Even lesbians?
Lesbians are women...
Sort of.
My mom says sometimes she
wished she never had me.
That's probably because she's stuck
with this annoying brat
for the rest of her life.
So... Are you going to raise him?
Me?
No way.
The munchers are.
But I'll be around to provide
the masculine influence
so important in every young boy's life.
I bet Melanie could
do it better than you.
Don't get smart or
I'll have to spank you.
Really?
You up for one more?
Brian!
Christ! Didn't you
get enough last night?
There is no such thing as enough.
Besides, I couldn't send him off
without a nourishing,
high-protein breakfast.
It's grrrreat!
Will you come on?
I'm not going to be late because of you.
I said hurry up!
Yeah, what did she say?
She said, "don't be late."
Oh, that's beautiful, Mikey.
Just beautiful.
It's not my fault.
I told you about those two
psychopaths down the street.
What, a couple of 12-year-olds?
They start early these days.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
You.
You sound like my parents fighting.
It doesn't matter anyway.
It's a company car.
Well, come on, we have to
take the child to school.
In this?
You care?
Fuck, no.
No way!
- Look at that.
- Look at this.
Here we are, Sonny Boy.
And be sure to come
home right after school.
No lingering on the playground
or in the locker room
with the gym teacher.
Oh, you did not tell him about that?
It's the most famous
shower scene since Psycho.
Hey, Justin!
You want to suck me off?
No, but I'll kick your tight
little virgin ass so hard
you won't sit down for a week.
Can we get out of here?
When can I see you again?
You can see me right now.
I mean later, tonight.
Who knows where I'll be later tonight.
Better go.
Please?
I'll see you in your dreams.
Oh, my God.
Where have you been?
Your mom called.
I didn't know what to tell her.
I said you were still asleep.
I just saw the face of God.
Huh?
His name is Brian Kinney.
Thank God he's finally gone.
He almost wore me out.
Somebody wore you out?
I said almost.
I'll drop you by the store.
Heh, the hell you will.
You better get this thing repainted
before you go into the office.
I'm not having it repainted.
What?
I like it this way.
Are you crazy?
No, they are.
Well, I say fuck 'em.
They can write it in
neon across the sky.
Faggot!
Ha ha!
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -